allindiajobs.in 2018-06-18

# Privacy Policy and DISCLAIMER | Freshers jobs | Experienced Jobs | Govt Jobs | Career Guidance | Results

February 27, 2012 by [Leave a Comment](http://www.allindiajobs.in/2012/02/disclaimer-all-india-jobs-jobs-in-india.html#respond)

### Disclaimer:

All the information on [www.allindiajobs.in](http://www.allindiajobs.in/) is published in **good faith** and for general information purpose only. **We collect information/jobs from various websites in which we don’t have control.** We do not make any warranties about the completeness, reliability and accuracy of this information provided on our portal. Any action you take upon the information on our website is strictly at your own risk. And we will not be liable for any losses and damages in connection with the use of our website.

**So we request job seekers, ****Please do thorough research before applying/attending to any job interview through our website.  **  
**  
** **  We take utmost care while publishing jobs on this site. But please keep in mind that we are also humans, so sometimes mistakes or errors might have crept in unintentionally. ** 

Note that certain links on this Site lead to resources located on servers maintained by third parties over whom we have no control and accordingly we accept no responsibility or liability for any of the material contained on those servers.

We make no warranty that the contents of the Site are free from infection by viruses or anything else which has contaminating or destructive properties and shall have no liability in respect thereof. 

**All the trademarks, trade names, logos or service marks mentioned or used on this site belong to their respective owners. We are using these logos just for information purpose only.**

If any respective owners of logo/trademark etc. don’t like to see their logo on our website or if it violates copyright norms, please write an e-mail to admin@allindiajobs.in. We will remove the trademark/logo from our website within 2 days.

[www.allindiajobs.in](http://www.allindiajobs.in/) and pages of the same website host advertising and other material submitted to us by third parties. Please note that those advertisers are responsible for ensuring that material submitted for inclusion on [www.allindiajobs.in](http://www.allindiajobs.in/) complies with all legal requirements. Although acceptance of advertisements on [www.allindiajobs.in](http://www.allindiajobs.in/) is subject to our terms and conditions which are available on request, we do not accept liability in respect of any advertisements. 

If you find any copyright infringement and the subject matter that is posted on this blog and you consider it as a violation of the copyright norms, please drop an email to **janardanraju@gmail.com**

**_Privacy Policy:_**

We use technologies like cookies, web beacons etc. to anonymously identify your computer or device to deliver a better experience. Our systems also log information like your browser, operating system and IP address. To customize our service for you, we may collect and store your precise geographic location as part of your user profile. This data generally is not shared with others. We may ask for your consent to your first use of the service. We don’t share your personal data with other companies.

We do not knowingly contact or collect personal information from children under 13. If you believe we have inadvertently collected such information, please contact us so we can promptly obtain parental consent or remove the information.

Ad companies may use and collect anonymous data about your interests to customize the content and advertising here and in other sites and applications. Interest and location data may be linked to your device, but is not linked to your identity.

We take reasonable steps to secure your personally identifiable information against unauthorized access or disclosure. We encrypt the transmission of data on pages where you provide payment information. However, no security or encryption method can be guaranteed to protect information from hackers or human error. Information we collect may be stored or processed on computers located in any country where we do business.

If you have any questions or concerns about our privacy policies, please contact us: admin@allindiajobs.in

**Thank you very much.**

## Reader Interactions
